Guide to the George B. Dantzig Papers
Stanford University Libraries.
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2005-363
  - NAS: Annual Meeting Washington, April 22-25 1990 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Design Aspects of a Convert Routine for a Large Scale Mathematical Programming System, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Standard L. P. Input Format, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Microcomputing with the Simplex Alsorithm (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Design Aspects of a Mathematical Programming System for Solving Large Scale Integer Programs, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Solving Systems of Equations, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Solution to Program #2 Gaussian Elimination, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Solution #2 Gaussian Elimination (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Solution to Program #2 Gaussian Elimination, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Problem #2, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Course Description; Freshman Year Seminar "Energy Crisis", 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Seminar 61- The Energy Crisis (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - A Selection of Possible Studies for the Energy Modeling Forum, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Preliminary Class List Energy Crisis, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Stanford New Directions Subscription, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Course Syllabus The Energy Crisis, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - New Directions in Foreign Policy Volume 1 Number 5, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Oil and Gas: the Core Issues, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Program Motzkin Fourier Elimination, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - CS 234 Notice, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - CS 234 Problem #3, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - CS 234 Problem #2, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - CS 234 Set #3, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - CS 234 Set #1, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Motzkin Fourier Elimination P.S. #6, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Minimum Cost Circulation P.S. #5, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Network Flow Theory (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Using External Procedures in MPL (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - CS 234 Solution #3 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - CS 234 Numerical Methods of Optimization, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - CS 234 Complementary Spanning Trees, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Compact Matrix-Inverse Scheme, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Representation of Inverse in Product Form (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Simplex Method (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Revised Simplex Method, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - CS 234 Simplex Algorithm, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - CS 234 Hou, Jen-Hon (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - CS 234 Assignment #4, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - CS 234 Solution #4 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - CS 234 Revised Assignment Schedule, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - CS 234 A Complex Matrix-Inverse Scheme, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - More on Compact- Inverse Scheme (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - A Compact Matrix-Inverse Scheme, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Revised Simplex Method, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Simplex Algorithm, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - CS 234 Hou, Jen-Hon (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Assignment #4, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - CS 234 Solution #4 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - CS 234 Revised Assignment Schedule, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - CS 234 Assignment #5 Simplex Algorithm, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - CS 234 Homework Assignment #3, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - CS 234 Comments, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Program Simplex Algorithm, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Examples that can be Solved by Dynamic Programming (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - CS 234 Dynamic Programming How To Drill an Oil Well, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Notation and Summary for the Simplex Method of Linear Programming, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Complementary Pivot Problem (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Game Thoery, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Maximal Flow Problem, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Proof of Shortest Spanning Tree, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Geometry, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - CS 234 Problem #1, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - CS234 Problem #1, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Generating Functions from Combinations (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Recurrence Relations Chapter 3 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Notes Chapter 1-2 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - What is Wrong with the Greedy Approach in General (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - A Proof of a Property of Leontief and Markov Matrices, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Simplex Algorithm Assignment #5, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Simplex Algorithm, Revised Simplex to be Coded as Homework, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Simplex Method Canonical Form, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Experiments on the Comparative Efficiency of the Various Variants of the Simplex Algorithm, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - CS 234 Solution #4 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - CS 234 Reduction to Canonical Form, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - CS 234 Example #1 Canonical Reduction (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - CS 234 Revised Simplex Algorithm, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Large Scale Linear Programming Notes for Tutorial Conference, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Ordinary Linear Program (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Knapsack and Cutting Stock Problem, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - CS 234 Homework Problem #1, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Autumn Quarter Enrollment Cards, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - CS 234 Network Flow Algorithm, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Example (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - OR340A Fact Sheet (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Graphs CS 234, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - CS 234 Use of Fourier-Motzkin Elimination Program, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - CS 234 Set #4 and 5 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - CS 234 Set #3, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Initialization (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Optimal Matrix Scaling (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Matrix Rescaling (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - P. S. #3 Matrix Scaling and Finding Basic Feasible Solution to H-K Transportation Problem, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Optimally Scaling a Matrix (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - On the Role of Congestion in Transportation Problems by William Prager, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - An Algorithm for Solving the Transporation Problem when the Shipping Cost Over Each Route is Convex, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - On the Automatic Scaling of Matrices for Gaussian Elimination, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - An Algorithm to Solve the m x n Assignment Problem in Expected Time O (mn log n)*, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Theoretical Improvements in Algorithmic Efficiency for Network Flow Problems, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Optimally Scaled Matrices F.L. Bauer, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - On Scaling Linear Programming Problems J. A. Tomlin, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Characterizations of Optimal Scalings of Matrices Uriel G. Rothblum, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - A Conforming Decomposition Theorem, a Piecewise Linear Theorem of the Alternative, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Starting Basis (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Diameters of Random Graphs Victor Klee and David Larman, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Expected Number of Vertices of a Random Convex Polytope I. Integral Formula and Asymptotic Rounds, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - E/ Joute CORE, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Let x1, x2,..., x(m+1) (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - The Expected Number of Pivots Required by the Simplex Algorithm in Solving Transhipment Problems, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Source Statement, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Runs Evaluating the Given Functions, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Expected Number of Steps of the Simplex Method for a Linear Program with a Convexity Constraint, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - University of Pittsburgh Dear Prof. Cottle, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - COMP In Our Own Image -A Computer Science Odyssey- by George B. Dantzig, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - CS 264 5 Hour Stanford University Class Roll Book, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - CS 234 Tentative Program Assignments and Due Dates, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - CS 234 Schedule of Autumn Quarter Classes, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - CS 234 SCIP Computer account, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - CS 234 Class List in Alphabetical Order by Name, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - CS 234 Class Notes, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - CS 234 Douglass O. Wilde Optimum Methods, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Motzkin Elimination (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Analytical Solution for Min-Max Intervals of Fabonocci Search (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Discrete Dynamic Programming Evolution (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Fibonacci Numbers (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - CS 234 Homework, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - CS 234 G. B. Dantzig Prepared by Leon Lasdon, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - CS 234 Homework Solutions Prepared by L. Lasdon, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - The Product Form of the Inverse, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - CS 234 One-Dimmensional Problem, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - CS 234 The State of the Art of Mathematical Programming by E M L Beale, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - CS 234 Cholesky Factorization, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Nonlinear Optimization Using the Generalized Reduced Gradient Method by Lasdon, Fox, Ratner, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Direct Methods for Constrained Problems (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Chapter 3 Constrained Problems by Unconstrained Minimization (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - An Article from Scientific American, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - CS 234 Course Questionnaire, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - CS 234 Course Outline, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - CS 234 Take Home Exam, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Numerical Methods in O. R. CS 234 Midterm, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - CS 234 Problem Session 1, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - CS 234 Problem Session 1, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - CS 234 SCIP Computer account, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - CS 234 Course Questionnaire, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - To: Prof. Dantzig From: Ralph Maltes Jr. RE: "Energy at Stanford", 1979 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Systems Optimization Laboratory (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - The Role of Models in Determining Policy for Transition to a More Resilient Technological Society, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Scientist and Engineers for Secure Energy Dear Prof. Dantzig, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Colloquium Abstract, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Oak Ridge National Laboratory Dear Prof. Dantzig, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Memorandum, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Energy, International Trade and Economic Development: A Mini Model, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Department of Operations Research Dear Prof. Carhart, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Integrating Time-Staged and Snap-Shot-in-Time Models for Policy Analysis and Technology Assessment Rough Draft (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Memorandum, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Why Look Ahead (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Pilot Process Integrated Model, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Department of Operations Research Dear Prof. Carhart Correspondence, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - The Components of a Technological Assessment of the Electric Vehicle (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - CS 234 Problem Set #1 Standard L. P. Input Format, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Office Memorandum, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - CS 234 Tentative Program Assessments and Due Dates, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Program written by Pierre de Mazancourt as Assignment 4 of CS 234 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - CS 234 General Information, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Program written by Pierre de Mazancourt as a Solution to CS 234 PS2 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Program written by Pierre de Mazancourt as a Solution to CS 234 PS3 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Program written by Pierre de Mazancourt as a Solution to CS 234 PS 4 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - CS 264 Ming-Lung Lee (5 Hour) Stanford University Class Roll Book (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Howard Wong-Toi 264 Final Clarification, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - CS 264 Final Examination Solutions, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - CS 264 Final Examination Blank, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Shortest Path Algorithm (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Harvard University Department of Economics Dear Prof. Dantzig, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - On Moore Graphs with Diameters 2 and 3, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - CS 264 Mid-Term, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - CS 264 Solutions of Mid-Term (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - CS 264 Tree of Shortest Paths, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - CS 264 Assignment 5, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - CS 264 Assignment 6, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - CS 264 Assignment 7, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Shortest Path Algorithm, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - CS 264 Introduction to Combinational Theory, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - CS 264 Assignment 1, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - CS 264 Solutions to Assignment 1 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - CS 264 Assignment 2, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Solutions to Assignment 2 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Solutions to Assignment 3 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - CS 264 Assignment 4, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Solutions to Assignment 4 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Linear Programming (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - CS 264 Final Examination, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - CS 264 Chapter 7 Recurrence Relations, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Dantzig Photographs (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - CS 264 Class List (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Class Material for CS 234, Fall 1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Class Material for OR 340A, October 1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Chapter 8, September 1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - How Bad is the Simplex Algorithm by Fu Ming Hui, 5/25/1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Copies of Comp Book, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Various papers concerning the simplex method, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Letter and Papers from Irvin Lustig, November 1991 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Prize, 1975-1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Curriculum Vitae, 1975, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Various Awards, 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Gail, 1974-1994 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Misc Citations for File, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Biography File, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Talk: London Math. Prog Symposium, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Large Scale Systems- Transparencies Talk, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Talk: About Computers and their applications - History, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Talk on AEC-DOD Interaction Model, 12/10/1953 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Exhibits of Sommendations and Professional Work, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - A Production Smoothing Problem, 12/13/1954 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Discussion Notes on a Continuous Version of the Dynamic Simplex Method, 3/2/1954 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Lower Cound for Minimum Value of a Linear Form, April 1954 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Composite Simplex Algorithm, 12/1/1954 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Upper Bounds, Secondary Constraints, and block triangularity in linear programming, April 1955 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Solution of a Large Scale Traveling Salesman Problem, 4/12/1954 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Speech on "Typical Military and Industrial Applications of Linear Programming" - ORSA San Francisco, 11/17/1956 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Maximal Lethal Pattern by George B. Dantzig, 3/25/1957 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Speech on LP and Automation RAND Board - Berkeley, 3/2/1956 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Minimizing the Number of Carriers to meet a fixed schedule - Chapter XVI, 8/8/1955 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Course and Conference, 7/9/1956 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Electric Power Appl., 10/18/1956 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Math Stat Integrals Continuous Formulation, 12/30/1955 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Elimination Form of Inverse, 4/8/1955 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Refinery Problems, undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Block Systems Secondary Constraints Single Block Structures, undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - The Substitute Inverse Method, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Multi-Stage Linear Programming (Given at Purdue), 5/8/1958 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Multi-Stage LP, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Speechs Honoring President Pitzer, 8/6/1970 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Dilworth's Theorem, undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Seminar- Programming and Game Theory, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Introd. Speech, undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Minimizing Tankers to Meet a Fixed Schedule, 8/8/1955 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - The Warehouse Problem, January 1957 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Scheduling a Tanker Fleet, 4/4/1958 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Product Form of Inverse, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - California Berkeley, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Allocation to Routes, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Uncertainty, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Communication Networks, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - A Simple Industrial Model, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Discrete Variable Extremum Problem, 16-Aug-55 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - A Mini-Max Criteria for Simplex Method (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Targeteer, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Linear Programming and Game Theory, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Board Speech (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Lecture 1: The Central Mathematical Problem (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Research Topics, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Diet Problem, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Linear Model of Production, 26-Feb-53 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - On the Status of Multi-Stage L.P. Problems + Princeton Conference, 14-Mar-57 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Notes on Block and Systems, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Dynamic Models - Thompsons Model, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Other IJK Problems, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Material Dropped or not Assigned, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - New Ideas (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Dantzig Stock Pile Problem, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - A General Inventory Problem, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Proof of Dual Theorem by the Simplex Method, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Game Theory, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Gas Company - Consulting, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Gass Dictionary, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - "Generalized Upper Bounds" - Technical File (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Historical Survey of Large Scale + Transparencies, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Support for Large Scale Systems, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - On Promising Developments in Mathematical Instruction (For California Secondary School Panel), 3/31/1958 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Integer Programs, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - IBM Min Cut of Directed Loops (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - "The Truck Dispatching Problem" G.B. Dantzig and J.H.Ramser, May-58 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - The Simplex Method, 7/9/1956 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Formulating a linear programming model, 7/9/1956 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Abstract of "Typical military and industrial applications of linear programming", 9/7/1956 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Abstract "An algorithm for block triangular linear programming systems", 9/7/1956 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - M-Step Problem (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - An Equivalent Linear Programming Problem, 1-Aug-58 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - On the Max Flow Min Cut Theorem of Networks, 15-Apr-55 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - An Algorithm for Solution of Certain Block Triangular LP Systems, 8/10/1955 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Chapter X- Scheduling, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Experiments with Transportation Methods of Solution (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - A Production Smoothing Problem, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Routing Aircraft - An Example of L.P. Under Uncertain Demand, 8/31/1955 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Example of Empty Container Problem, 9/1/1955 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Note on B. Klein's "Direct Use of Extremal Principles in Solving Certain Problems Involving Inequalities", Nov. 1955 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - A Primal- Dual Algorithm, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - The Allocationof Aircraft to Routes--an example of linear programming under uncertain demand, 1/12/1956 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - An Algorithm for the Solution of Certain Block Triangular Linear Programming Systems, 2/28/1956 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Flood Gun-Target allocation problem, 4/5/1957 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Max Flows in Networks, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - "Optimum Routing of Gasoline Delivery Trucks", 5/31/1959 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Computing Tel in L.R. Format, 6/26/1959 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - On the Status of Multistage Linear Programming Problems, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - A Linear Programming Approach to the chemical equilibrium Problem, 4/15/1957 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Upper Bounded Variables in Linear Programming, 4/24/1957 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Into the Wild Blue Yonder - encore, 5/1/1957 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Computing Tetraethyl Lead Requirements in the Linear Programming Format, 5/9/1957 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Chemical Equilibrium in Complex Mixtures, 5/10/1957 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - General Suggestions on Solving Transp. Problems on a mod. Speed computer, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - On a linear programming-combinatorial approach to the traveling salesman problem, 2/14/1958 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - On Gales Bargaining Model, Mar-58 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Notes on L.P. Computation of Maximal Flows in Network, 4/1/1955 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - New Directions of Mathematical Programming, 16-Mar-59 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - System Science Inst. Proposal, 18-Mar-63 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Centre, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - ACM-SIGMAC, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Symposium on Math. Optimization Techniques of RAND - UCLA, Oct-60 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Abstract of Concepts, Origins, and use of Linear Programming, 11/19/1956 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Notes on linear programming: Part XXXVI, 12/7/1956 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Discrete-variable extremum problems, 12/12/1956 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - An Experiment on neighbor relations of vertices, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Note on B. Klein's "Direct Use of Extremal Principles in Solving Certain Problems, etc. Involving Inequalities", 1/29/1957 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Talk-Notes Misc. (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Talks American Math.Soc. Talk Reno, Apr-64 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - "A Generalized Upper-Bounded Techniques for Linear Programming - Technical File (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - A Simple Industrial Model, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - RE Charnes of GDB + Wolf + Decomp, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - (Not lableled) Investment Problem, Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - (Not labeled) 62.15, Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Solution of a Large-Scale Traveling Salesman Problem, Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Complementary Notes, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - A Linear Programming Approach to the chemical equilibrium Problem, 4/21/1958 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - On Integer and Partial Integers Linear Programming Problems, 6/20/1958 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Chemical Equil. Progblem Using DP-Cook Book Procedure, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Shapley's Problem Equil. for Non-zero sum 2 person game, November 1959 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Talks: Non-linear Program Decomp. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Dynamic Optimization (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - History, Large-Scale, Undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Talks: Large-Scale System Studies (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Talk: "Control Theory" talk - technical file, 7/17/65-7/20/65 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - On the Error in the Von Neumann Convex Body Method, June 1948 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Letters to Tucker, 7/20/1948 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Notes on Dynamic Personnel, December 1947 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - BINAC Coding of Triangular Model, Spring 1949 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - (Danztig + Wood) Prog. of Inter-Dependent Activities - General Discussion, March 1949 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Progress Report on High-Speed Computation of Programs, 6/10/1949 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Proof of reduction of a program to a game, 6/8/1949 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Need for High Speed Electronic Computers for Programming, 8/22/1949 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Max Linear Form...Subject to Linear Inequalities, 11/1/1949 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Commens on Koopmans Efficient Allocation of Resources, 10/3/1950 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Discussion of an Antibiotic Problem, Fall 1950 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Dept. Agriculture Course Notes on 22 Survey of Linear Programming, Fall 1950 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Linear Programming on the SEAC Paper- Assoc. Computing Machinery, 9/7/1950-9/9/1950 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Discussion of a Chemical Problem, 10/20/1950 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Linear Prog. Activities in Wash, 10/28/1950 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - G.W. Logistics Seminar paper (Notes on SCOOP), January 1951 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Notes on Degeneracy, March 1951-1952 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Computation of Triangular Models, April 1951 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Talk before SCOOP Seminar - "Bringing up a large scale computer", 6/8/1951 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Programming Production to Cover Variable Requirements, 7/26/1951 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Initial Discussion with Marshall K. Wood (and Original Notes), 1947 (Box 9, Folder 36)